[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66eaf2153f35b9334627ac39"
  },
  "type": "simple",
  "question": "How do you say “gato” in English?",
  "answer": "cat",
  "points": 10,
  "level": "Elementary"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66eaf3363f35b9334627ac41"
  },
  "type": "simple",
  "question": "What is the plural of “book”?",
  "answer": "books",
  "points": 10,
  "level": "Elementary"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66eaf3963f35b9334627ac42"
  },
  "type": "simple",
  "question": "What is the past tense of “play”?",
  "answer": "played",
  "points": 10,
  "level": "Elementary"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66eaf3ac3f35b9334627ac43"
  },
  "type": "simple",
  "question": "What is the opposite of “tall”?",
  "answer": "short",
  "points": 10,
  "level": "Elementary"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66eaf3ae3f35b9334627ac44"
  },
  "type": "multiple",
  "question": "What is the correct form of the verb in this sentence? She ____ to the park every day.",
  "options": [
    "go",
    "goes",
    "going",
    "gone"
  ],
  "answer": "goes",
  "points": 10,
  "level": "Elementary"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66eaf4b73f35b9334627ac45"
  },
  "type": "multiple",
  "question": "Which word is a color?",
  "options": [
    "table",
    "quickly",
    "blue",
    "sing"
  ],
  "answer": "blue",
  "points": 10,
  "level": "Elementary"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66eaf51e3f35b9334627ac46"
  },
  "type": "multiple",
  "question": "Which sentence is correct?",
  "options": [
    "She are happy",
    "They is happy",
    "I am happy",
    "He am happy"
  ],
  "answer": "I am happy",
  "points": 10,
  "level": "Elementary"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66eaf5a73f35b9334627ac47"
  },
  "type": "multiple",
  "question": "Which word completes this sentence correctly? I ____ reading a book",
  "options": [
    "is",
    "are",
    "am",
    "be"
  ],
  "answer": "am",
  "points": 10,
  "level": "Elementary"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66eaf6573f35b9334627ac4a"
  },
  "type": "video",
  "question": "Record a video talking about your family members",
  "points": "20",
  "level": "Elementary"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66ef9fc685bc098b97a9c827"
  },
  "type": "simple",
  "question": "¿Cuál es la capital de Francia?",
  "answer": "París",
  "points": 5,
  "level": "Elementary",
  "createdAt": {
    "$date": "2024-09-22T04:40:38.204Z"
  },
  "updatedAt": {
    "$date": "2024-09-22T04:40:38.204Z"
  },
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66f1c5b132e29418caa13418"
  },
  "type": "simple",
  "question": "¿Cuál es la capital de Francia2?",
  "answer": "París2",
  "points": 15,
  "level": "Elementary",
  "createdAt": {
    "$date": "2024-09-23T19:46:57.730Z"
  },
  "updatedAt": {
    "$date": "2024-09-23T19:46:57.730Z"
  },
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66f4ab4d1e467eb275ba5a62"
  },
  "type": "Pregunta Simple",
  "question": "Prueba?",
  "answer": "Si",
  "points": 10,
  "level": "Elementary",
  "createdAt": {
    "$date": "2024-09-26T00:31:09.495Z"
  },
  "updatedAt": {
    "$date": "2024-09-26T00:31:09.495Z"
  },
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66f4d85b1e50909bd9bdc81a"
  },
  "type": "simple",
  "question": "Prueba nose",
  "answer": "se",
  "points": 50,
  "level": "Elementary",
  "createdAt": {
    "$date": "2024-09-26T03:43:23.761Z"
  },
  "updatedAt": {
    "$date": "2024-09-26T03:43:23.761Z"
  },
  "__v": 0
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66f5a62d0f123e5f3cb84d8b"
  },
  "type": "simple",
  "question": "¿Cuál es la capital de Francia2?",
  "answer": "París2",
  "points": 15,
  "level": "Elementary",
  "createdAt": {
    "$date": "2024-09-26T18:21:33.486Z"
  },
  "updatedAt": {
    "$date": "2024-09-26T18:21:33.486Z"
  },
  "__v": 0
}]